When my husband was going into the dining room this morning,
今天早晨我丈夫走进饭厅时,
he dropped some coins on the floor.
他把一些硬币掉在地上了.
There were coins everywhere.
到处都是硬币.
We looked for them, but we could not find them all.
我们找了,但没有把它们全部找到.
While we were having breakfast,
正当我们吃早饭时,
our little boy, Tommy, found two small coins on the floor.
我们的小男孩Tommy在地上找到了两枚小硬币.
He put them both into his mouth.
他把那两枚硬币都放进了嘴里.
We both tried to get the coins, but it was too late.
我们俩都试图把这两枚硬币拿出来,但太迟了.
Tommy had already swallowed them!
汤米已经把硬币咽了下去!
Later that morning, when I was doing the housework,
那天下午的晚些时候,当我正做家务时,
My husband phoned me from the office.
我丈夫从办公室打来电话.
How's Tommy?' he asked.
“汤米怎么样?”他问.
I don't know,' I answered,
“我不知道”,我回答说,
Tommy's been to the toilet three times this morning,
“今天上午汤米去了3次厕所了,
but I haven't had any change yet!'
但我还没看到硬币!”